zbrushtuts.com 2018-11-21

# Privacy Policy – zbrushtuts

This Privacy Policy describes the information collected by Zbrushtuts  (“zbrushtuts”  “we”, “us” or “our”) through our email subscription and how we use that information.

### **We Collect Limited Information With Our email subscription.**

When you subscribe to zbrushtuts we require you to provide limited information ie email adress and we don’t collect any information except email adress of person. And subscripbed email are for those persons who wish to receive regular updates on tutorials, news or other zbrush content and also to receive our newsletter. With those email addresses used solely to send the newsletter.

### **When You Request Support, You May Send Us Email**

We allow users to contact us if they have support questions about content of website. Or if they wanted their tutorials or other related content on our website.

### **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We use Support Information only for the support for the internal operations of our website. We don’t rent, sell or share your email address.

### **Cookies**

We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking usage information. Most browsers allow you to disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.

### **Links to Third Party Sites**

We may provide links and/or connections to third-party web sites or services from our website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these third-party sites.

#### **Some of the website we provide links of:**

**Affiliated channels**

<https://rakutenmarketing.com/>

**Ad Networks**

https://www.google.com/adsense

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use your email address, we will notify you in advance of posting by email. Such modifications will become effective on the date set forth in the email.

### **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please send us an email at admin[at]zbrushtuts[dot]com.
